const A=[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],I=[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}],E={music:A,"modern-art":[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:["Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Fauvism","Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:["Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:["Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse","Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Pablo Picasso"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],coding:I};function z(e){let o=[];return e.forEach(t=>{o.push(t.answer)}),o}function W(e,o){for(let t=0;t<e.length;t++){let n=document.createElement("div"),d=document.createElement("input"),q=document.createElement("label");n.classList.add("option-item"),d.name="answer",d.type="radio",d.id=e[t],d.value=e[t],q.textContent=e[t],q.setAttribute("for",e[t]),n.appendChild(d),n.appendChild(q),o.appendChild(n)}}function k(e){let o=[];for(let t=0;t<e.length;t++){let n=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length);if(o.includes(e[n]))return k(e);o.push(e[n])}return o}function b(e){let o=[];for(let t=0;t<e.length;t++){let n=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length);if(o.includes(e[n]))return b(e);o.push(e[n])}return o}const D=document.querySelector(".navbar"),p=document.querySelector(".quiz-container"),O=document.querySelector(".form-container"),f=document.querySelectorAll(".topic-item"),H=document.querySelectorAll(".topic-item .topic"),J=document.querySelector(".start-btn"),h=document.querySelector(".submit-btn"),y=document.querySelector(".quit-btn button"),j=document.querySelector(".play-again-btn"),M=document.querySelector(".topic-title"),g=document.querySelector(".question p"),r=document.querySelector(".options"),F=document.querySelector(".quiz"),w=document.querySelector(".time"),v=document.querySelector(".end-message .message"),C=document.querySelector(".final-result"),S=document.querySelector(".end-message"),G=document.querySelector(".result-btn");let B=document.querySelector(".username");const l=document.querySelector(".alert"),x=document.querySelector(".alert p");localStorage.getItem("user")&&(B.textContent=localStorage.getItem("user"));let a="",i="",L=[],m=[],c,u=15;function P(){for(let e=0;e<f.length;e++)f[e].addEventListener("click",()=>{document.querySelector(".selected")&&document.querySelector(".selected").classList.remove("selected"),f[e].classList.add("selected"),M.textContent=f[e].textContent+" Quiz",M.style.color="white",a=H[e].textContent.toLowerCase().split(" ").join("-"),a==="coding"&&(p.style.backgroundColor="#ffb703"),a==="modern-art"&&(p.style.backgroundColor="#023047"),a==="music"&&(p.style.backgroundColor="#219ebc"),i=E[a],i=k(i),m=z(i)})}function T(){if(a!==""){O.classList.add("inactive"),D.classList.add("inactive"),g.textContent=i[s].question;let e=b(i[s].options);W(e,r),F.classList.add("active"),p.classList.remove("inactive"),c=setInterval(()=>{u===0&&(g.textContent="",r.innerHTML="",h.classList.add("inactive"),y.classList.add("inactive"),S.classList.remove("inactive"),v.textContent="Oh! You went out of Time. Please Try Again.",clearInterval(c)),w.textContent=u--},1e3)}else{l.classList.remove("inactive"),x.textContent="Please Select a Topic",l.style.backgroundColor="red";let e=setTimeout(()=>{l.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(e)},3e3)}}P();let s=0;J.addEventListener("click",()=>{console.log("hello"),T()});h.addEventListener("click",()=>{let e=document.querySelectorAll(".active .options .option-item input"),o=!1;if(e.forEach(t=>{t.checked===!0&&(L.push(t.value),o=!0)}),o)if(s+1===i.length)g.textContent="",r.innerHTML="",h.classList.add("inactive"),y.classList.add("inactive"),S.classList.remove("inactive"),v.textContent="Well Done! You answered All the Questions.",clearInterval(c),w.textContent=0;else{clearInterval(c),s++,g.textContent=i[s].question,r.innerHTML="";let t=b(i[s].options);W(t,r),u=15,c=setInterval(()=>{u===0&&(g.textContent="",r.innerHTML="",h.classList.add("inactive"),y.classList.add("inactive"),S.classList.remove("inactive"),v.textContent="Oh! You went out of Time. Please Try Again.",clearInterval(c)),w.textContent=u--},1e3)}else{l.classList.remove("inactive"),x.textContent="Please Select an Option",l.style.backgroundColor="red";let t=setTimeout(()=>{l.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(t)},3e3)}});G.addEventListener("click",()=>{let e=0;w.textContent=0,L.forEach((t,n)=>{t===m[n]&&e++}),C.textContent=`${e} out of ${m.length}`,C.style.color="green";let o=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("userTrack"));o?(localStorage.removeItem("userTrack"),localStorage.setItem("userTrack",JSON.stringify([{topic:a,userAnswer:e,totalScore:m.length,date:new Date().toLocaleString()},...o]))):localStorage.setItem("userTrack",JSON.stringify([{topic:a,userAnswer:e,totalScore:m.length,date:new Date().toLocaleString()}]))});j.addEventListener("click",()=>{s=0,u=15,L=[],h.classList.remove("inactive"),y.classList.remove("inactive"),S.classList.add("inactive"),C.textContent="",v.textContent="",P(),T()});
